{
    "id": "d09e00f3a0dd4c50956f8f3c94c1fd50",
    "title": "Tenses | Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It ...................... raining for two hours.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has been",
                "have been",
                "is",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "56658a03a3d8499ea9aa3efcaa34e6a4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................... .. my grandmother yesterday.",
            "description": "We use the simple past tense to talk about something we did in the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "visited",
                "have visited",
                "had visited",
                "was visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ce8bde8fb8e9405abfb16db4432e3fb2"
        },
        {
            "question": "My boss ..................... from London.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "returned",
                "has returned",
                "had returned",
                "have returned"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4794368b726a47e487127f9467ed6efc"
        },
        {
            "question": "See that you ..................... . on time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will arrive",
                "would arrive",
                "arrive",
                "arrived"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8ac8efde2bd844fd9bec6df57207003e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She will come if you .....................…… her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "invite",
                "invited",
                "would invite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9c64c88517384e2c9a1ec2f7f1a85220"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .....................…… to Iceland recently.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "have been",
                "had been",
                "Either went or had been"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "c2014373355748c0af6518ef92e1e53e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor concluded that the man .....................… killed ten hours ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "have been",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6ad9047789144d1a92faa410a75f7555"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ..................... . waiting for them for two weeks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have been",
                "had been",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8ed2a578ea234ee7a1ae8c2b538ae543"
        },
        {
            "question": "The train .....................…. before we reached the station.",
            "description": "We use the past perfect for the earlier of the two past actions.",
            "answers": [
                "will leave",
                "will have left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7028904d0d0545c998794bd5091bceee"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ....................... the newspaper every morning.",
            "description": "We use the simple present tense to talk about habitual actions in the present. ",
            "answers": [
                "am reading",
                "will read",
                "read",
                "have read"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f4950fbc590542b6973ee1a3035feb86"
        }
    ]
}